■ seongmin@gatech.edu | # ligi214.github.io | ■ Seongmin Lee | ■ @SeongminLeee

Summary_

I'm a Ph.D. student in Computer Science at Georgia Tech, advised by Professor Polo Chau. My research interests cover data mining and machine learning; specifically, graph mining, ML interpretability, and real-world programming. I received my B.S. in Electrical and Computer Engineering from Seoul National University in February 2021.

Education

Georgia Institute of Technology

Georgia, USA

Ph.D. IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Aug. 2021 - Present

Advisor: Prof. Duen Horng (Polo) Chau

Seoul National University

Seoul, South Korea

B.S. IN ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING Graduated with honor (Summa Cum Laude)

Mar. 2016 - Feb. 2021

Korea Science Academy of KAIST

Busan, South Korea

MATH AND SCIENCE SPECIALIZED HIGH SCHOOL

Feb. 2013 - Feb. 2016

One year early entrance, Graduated with distinction in GPA

Research Experience

Polo Club of Data Science, Georgia Institute of Technology

Georgia, USA

GRADUATE RESEARCH ASSISTANT

Aug. 2021 - Present

- Advisor: Prof. Duen Horng (Polo) Chau
- Member of the Polo Club of Data Science where we innovate scalable, interactive, and interpretable tools that amplify human's ability to understand and interact with billion-scale data and machine learning models.

Data Mining Lab, Seoul National University

Seoul, South Korea

Undergraduate Research Internship

Jan. 2020 - Feb. 2021

- · Advisor: Prof. U Kang
- Studied multi-source domain adaptation under various constraints and settings
- Investigated the problem of BERT that the tasks with few training data are hard to fine-tune and solved it using reinforcement learning

Communication and Machine Learning Laboratory, Seoul National University

Seoul, South Korea

Undergraduate Research Internship and Bachelor's Thesis

Sep. 2019 - Apr. 2020

- Advisor: Prof. Jungwoo Lee
- Studied the problem of class imbalance and uncertainty in semantic segmentation

Biomedical Precision Laboratory, The University of Tokyo

Tokyo, Japan

Undergraduate Research Internship

Jul. 2018 - Aug. 2018

- · Advisor: Dr. Keiichi Nakagawa, Dr. Ayumu Ishijima.
- Observed interaction between human cell and acoustic wave by constructing a microscopic motion-picture camera with sub-nano resolution using optical equipment and laser

Publications

Multi-EPL: Accurate Multi-Source Domain Adaptation

Seongmin Lee, Hyunsik Jeon, and U Kang

PLOS ONE, 2021

AUBER: Automated BERT Regularization

Hyun Dong Lee*, **Seongmin Lee***, and U Kang (* These authors contributed equally to this work)

Unsupervised Multi-Source Domain Adaptation with No Observable Source Data

Hyunsik Jeon, Seongmin Lee, and U Kang

PLOS ONE, 2021

SEPTEMBER 7, 2021 SEONGMIN LEE · RÉSUMÉ

Patent

Pruning Method for Attention Head in Transformer Neural Networks for Regularization and Apparatus Thereof

Seongmin Lee, Hyun Dong Lee, and U Kang

10-2020-0162397, 2020

Honors & Awards

The Presidential Science Scholarship

Mar. 2016 - Dec. 2019

KOREA SCIENCE AID FOUNDATION

SNU Engineering Honor Society (STEM)

Mar. 2018 - Dec. 2019

COLLEGE OF ENGINEERING, SNU, USED TO BE VICE PRESIDENT, CURRENTLY HONORARY MEMBER.

Voluntary Service Award

Dec. 2018, Dec. 2017

DEPARTMENT OF ELECTRICAL AND COMPUTER ENGINEERING, SNU

Teaching_

Deep Learning Course for LG Chem, Lab session lecturer

Jan. 2021

Jul. 2019

Feb. 2019, Feb. 2018

Deep Learning Course for SK Hynix, Lab session lecturer

Nov. 2020

Introduction to Algorithm, SNU, Undergraduate student tutor

Fall 2020, Fall 2019

Introduction to Physics I, SNU, Undergraduate student tutor

Spring 2017

Skills

Programming C/C++, Python, Java, Verilog, HTML/CSS

Frameworks Tensorflow, PyTorch

Languages Korean (Native), English (iBT: 109 (R28/L28/S26/W27), GRE: Verbal 163, Writing 4.5)

Extracurricular Activity _____

SNU Buddy Sep. 2020 - Dec. 2020

Buddy program for the international exchange students. Used to be a group leader.

Vision Mentoring, Seoul National University

Organized and gave lecture on engineering for high school students (More than 700 students attended)

Dream Camp Mentoring, Seoul National University

 $Conducted\ mentoring\ program\ about\ "how\ to\ materialize\ one's\ dream"\ for\ high\ school\ students\ in\ countryside$

Student Vice President

Nov. 2017 - Oct. 2018

Elected as a vice president of the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering, SNU

Student Reporter Sep. 2017 - Feb. 2021

Published brochures about the Department of Electrical and Computer Engineering every semester

Talent Sharing Volunteer Camp, KOSAF

Jan. 2017, Aug. 2016

Conducted self-planned mentoring for elementary school students in underprivileged areas in Korea